Guide to the Joseph Urban Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: New York
  - Subseries III.3: Theater, 1914-1933
    - The Love Letter, October 4, 1921:
      - 1 program (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Blaue Mazur, 1921:
      Urban had agreed to design the Lehar operetta for Henry W. Savage. The project was canceled after Urban and Savage had a disagreement regarding the sets for The Merry Widow.
      - Director's playbook (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Yankee Princess, October 2, 1922:
      Musical comedy adapted from the Viennese operetta Die Bajadere by Julius Brammer and Alfred Grünwald, with book by William Le Baron, lyrics by B. G. De Sylva, music by Emmerich Kalman, choreographed by Julian Mitchell, directed by Fred G. Latham, produced by A. L. Erlanger at the Knickerbocker Theater with Vivienne Segal and Thorpe Bates. 80 performances.
      - 3 set renderings, watercolor and pencil:
      - --Act I: Theater Lobby, 21x31 (16x25) cm. (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - --Act II: Princess Room, 20x30 (16x25) cm. (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - --Act III: Club room, 21x31 (16x25) cm. (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - 4 technical drawings (Box 14-9-2, Folder 10)
    - Dream Girl, August 20, 1924:
      The premiere of this musical, produced by Lee and J. J. Shubert at the Ambassador Theater and starring Fay Bainter was designed by Watson Barratt.
      - Script notes (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Orpheum Circuit, 1925:
      - 3 blueprints (Box D3, Folder 9)
      - 14 drawings, watercolor and pencil:
      - --Garden, 26x32 (15x23) cm. (Box B7, Folder 2)
      - --Mountain panorama, 25x33 (13x21) cm. (Box B7, Folder 3)
      - --Pavilion, 25x33 (13x21) cm. (Box B7, Folder 4)
      - --Club room, 25x32 (16x25) cm. (Box B7, Folder 5)
      - --Terrace, 26x36 (13x21) cm. (Box B7, Folder 6)
      - --Library, 23x35 (13x21) cm. (Box B7, Folder 7)
      - --White interior, 26x33 (13x21) cm. (Box B7, Folder 8)
      - --Drawing room drop, 26x31 (13x21) cm. (Box B7, Folder 9)
      - --Street Scene, 24x35 (18x29) cm. (Box B7, Folder 10)
      - --Oriental city, 25x33 (19x29) cm. (Box B7, Folder 11)
      - --Park drop, 26x31 (14x22) cm. (Box B7, Folder 12)
      - --Drawing room, 26x31 (13x21) cm. (Box B7, Folder 13)
      - --Portal, not used, 23x31 (16x27) cm. (Box B7, Folder 14)
      - --Conservatory, 26x31 (13x21) cm. (Box B7, Folder 15)
      - 1 scaled drawing of eagle (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Mayflower Hotel Stage Setting, 1925:
      - 2 drawings, watercolor and pencil:
      - --Woman fg., street scene (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - --Champs Elysees, 21x26 (11x16) cm. (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - --stage setting, 22x25 cm (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - 9 technical drawings (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - 11 technical drawings (Box 14-9-2, Folder 11)
      - 1 drawing of slouching panther (Box 14-9-2, Folder 11)
      - 1 photograph of stage setting (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Human Nature (Gun Powder), September 24, 1925:
      Comedy in 3 acts by J. C. and Elliott Nugent, produced by Gene Buck, directed by J. C. Nugent and Frederick Stanhope with Mary Duncan, Brandon Tynan, John Marston and Frank Conroy at the Liberty Theater. 4 performances
      - 3 technical drawings (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - 1 job order (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - 7 technical drawings (Box 14-9-2, Folder 12)
      - Set model
    - Tale of the Wolf, October 7, 1925:
      Comedy in 3 acts by Ferenc Molnar, produced by Charles Frohman Inc., directed by Frank Reicher at the Empire Theater with Phyllis Povah, Roland Young and Wallace Eddinger. 13 performances.
      - 2 drawings, watercolor and pencil:
      - --Act I: Cabaret interior, 26x31 (17x25) cm. (Box B8, Folder 1)
      - --Act II: Room, Kelemen House, 22x33 (17x11) cm. (Box B8, Folder 2)
      - 9 sketches & notes (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - 11 technical drawings (Box 14-9-2, Folder 13)
      - Set model
    - Antonia, October 20, 1925:
      Written by Melchior Lengyel, adapted by Arthur Richman, directed by George Cukor, produced by Charles Frohman, Inc. with Marjorie Rambeau at the Empire Theater. 55 performances.
      - 12 technical drawings (Box 14-9-2, Folder 14)
      - 2 sketches of details (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - 2 photographs of set drawings (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Program (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Song of the Flame, December 30, 1925:
      Romantic opera in prologue, two acts and epilogue, book and lyrics by Otto Harbach and Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Herbert Stothart and George Gershwin, costumes by Mark Mooring, choreographed by Jack Haskell, produced by Arthur Hammerstein, directed by Frank Reicher at the Forty-fourth Street Theater with Tessa Kosta as Aniuta and Guy Robertson as Volodya. 224 performances.
      - 33 technical drawings (Box 14-9-2, Folder 15)
      - I.5: Elevation (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - 2 programs (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - Set model
    - Duchess of Elba, 1925-1926:
      Written by Rudolph Lothar.
      - 3 watercolor drawings by Gretl Urban, sig.:
      - --Act I: Store scene, 19x29 (10x20) cm. (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - --Act II: Sitting Room, 18x29 (10x18) cm. (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - --Act III: Bedroom, 19x29 (12x25) cm. (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - 6 technical drawings (Box 14-9-2, Folder 16)
      - 2 set sketches (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - 1 sketch of Napoleon (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - 1 wallpaper sample (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - Set model
    - Wild Rose (Hawthorne of the USA), October 20, 1926:
      Musical comedy in 2 acts, book and lyrics by Otto Harbach and Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Rudolf Friml, choreographed by Busby Berkeley, costumes by Mark Mooring, directed by William J. Wilson, produced by Arthur Hammerstein at the Martin Beck Theater with Joseph Santley, Desiree Ellinger and William Collier. 61 performances.
      - 8 drawings, watercolor and pencil:
      - --ActI.1: Casino, not used, 27x33 (12x18) cm. (Box B8, Folder 3)
      - --Act I.2:Inn Front, 25x31 (12x19) cm. (Box B8, Folder 4)
      - --Act I.3: Tavern, 26x31 (12x18) cm. (Box B8, Folder 5)
      - --Act I.4: Garden Wall, 26x31 (13x18) cm. (Box B8, Folder 6)
      - --Act II.1:King's Dressing Room, 26x31 (12x20) cm. (Box B8, Folder 7)
      - --Act II.2: Castle yard, 26x31 (12x18) cm. (Box B8, Folder 8)
      - --Act II.3: Tower, 26x31 (12x18) cm. (Box B8, Folder 9)
      - --Act II.4: Border drop, 26x31 (13x18) cm., signed by Gretl (Box B8, Folder 10)
      - Sketches and notes, 6 p. (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - 28 technical drawings (Box 14-9-2, Folder 17)
      - 4 detail sketches of throne room (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - Letter from construction co. (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - Set models
    - Yours Truly (Lotus Flower), January 25, 1927:
      Musical play in 2 acts, book and lyrics by Clyde North and Anne Caldwell, music by Raymond Hubbell, choreographed by Ralph Reader, produced by Gene Buck, directed by Paul Dickey at the Shubert Theater with Leon Errol, Marion Harris, Ina Williams and Irene Dunne. 129 performances. Restaged at the Century Theater for 16 performances March 12, 1928.
      - 5 drawings, watercolor and pencil:
      - --Green curtain, 26x31 (14x20) cm. (Box B8, Folder 11)
      - --I: Mission Square, 26x31 (15x19) cm. (Box B8, Folder 12)
      - --II.1: Garden, 25x31 (14x22) cm. (Box B9, Folder 2)
      - --II.3 Mission interior, 26x31 (13x19) cm. (Box B8, Folder 13)
      - --II.5: Cabaret, 24x28 (13x19) cm. (Box B9, Folder 1)
      - 2 set sketches (Box 14, Folder 19)
      - 18 technical drawings (Box 14-9-3, Folder 1)
      - 16 photographs of set drawings and set (Box 14, Folder 19)
      - Program (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Golden Dawn, November 30, 1927.:
      Musical drama in 2 acts by Otto Harbach and Oscar Hammerstein, II, music by Emmerich Kalman and Herbert Stothart, choreographed by Dave Bennett, costumes by Mark Mooring, directed by Reginald Hammerstein, produced by Arthur Hammerstein at Hammerstein Theater with Louise Hunter, Robert Chisholm, Paul Gregory and Archie Leach (Cary Grant). 184 performances.
      - Sketches & notes, 12 p. (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - 3 drawings, watercolor and pencil:
      - --Straw Curtain, 22x22 cm. (Box A1, Folder 21)
      - --Act I.4: Magic Tree, 26x32 (13x19) cm. (Box B9, Folder 3)
      - --Act II.4: Mission, Finale A, 26x31 (13x20) cm. (Box B9, Folder 4)
      - 31 technical drawings (Box 14-9-3, Folder 2 & 3)
      - 9 photographs of set drawings (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Set model
    - Big Parade, MGM, 1925:
      Art direction by James Basevi and Cedric Gibbons. In 1928 plans were made to make a musical for which Urban was to design the set.
      - 83 photographs of scenes and publicity stills (Box 27, Folder 19 & 20)
    - Treasure Girl, November 8, 1928:
      Musical comedy in 2 acts, book by Fred Thompson and Vincent Lawrence, lyrics by Ira Gershwin, music by George Gershwin, directed by Bertram Harrison, choreographed by Bobby Connolly, produced by Alex A. Aarons and Vinton Freedley at the Alvin Theater with Gertrude Lawrence, Walter Catlett, Clifton Webb and Mary Hay. 68 performances.
      - 1 drawing, watercolor and pencil:
      - --Curtain, 28x38 cm. (Box B9, Folder 5)
      - 9 sketches & notes (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - 19 technical drawings (Box 14-9-3, Folder 4)
      - 9 photographs of sets (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Set model
    - Polly, January 8, 1929:
      Musical in 2 acts by Guy Bolton and George Middleton of the 1917 comedy Polly with a Past, music and lyrics by Herbert Stothart, Philip Charig and Irving Caesar, directed by John Harwood, choreographed by Jack Haskell, produced by Arthur Hammerstein at the Lyric Theater with June, Charles Esdale and Fred Allen. 15 performances.
      - 1 drawing, watercolor and pencil:
      - --Western Union Office (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - 7 technical drawings (Box 14-9-3, Folder 5)
      - Set model
    - Sons O' Guns (Tin Hats), November 26, 1929:
      Musical comedy by Fred Thompson and Jack Donahue, music and lyrics by Arthur Swanstrom, Benny Davis and J. Fred Coots, choreographed by Bobby Connolly and Albertina Rasch, costumes by Charles Le Maire, directed by Bobby Connolly, produced by Connolly and Swanstrom at the Imperial Theater with Jack Donahue, William Frawley and Lily Damita. 295 performances
      - 1 reference photo (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - 20 sketches & notes (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - 52 technical Drawings (Box 14-9-3, Folder 6)
      - 19 photographs of sets (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Set model
    - Ripples, February 11, 1930:
      Musical comedy in 2 acts by William Anthony McGuire, music by Oscar Levant and Albert Sirmay, lyrics by Irving Caesar and Graham John, costumes by Charles LeMaire choreographed by William Holbrook, directed by William Anthony McGuire, produced by Charles Dillingham at the New Amsterdam with Fred Stone, Dorothy Stone, Paula Stone, Charles Collins, and Eddie Foy, Jr. 55 performances.
      - Scene IV set notes, 21 p. (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - 44 technical drawings (Box 14-9-3, Folder 7)
      - 4 detail drawings (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - 4 photographs of sets (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Set models
    - Flying High, March 3, 1930:
      Musical comedy in 2 acts, book and lyrics by B. G. DeSylva, Lew Brown and John McGowan, music by DeSylva, Brown and Ray Henderson, costumes by Charles LeMaire, choreographed by Bobby Connolly, directed by Edward Clark Lilley, produced by George White at the Apollo Theater with Bert Lahr, Kate Smith, Grace Brinkley and Oscar Shaw. 357 performances.
      - 1 set list (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - 2 drawings-pencil (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - 47 technical drawings (Box 14-9-3, Folder 8)
      - 13 photographs of sets (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - 1 program (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - 3 exhibit notes (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Set models
    - Princess Charming, October 13, 1930:
      Romantic opera in 2 acts adapted by Jack Donahue from the original by Franz Martos, Arthur Wimperis and Laurie Wylie, music by Albert Sirmay and Arthur Swartz, lyrics by Arthur Swanstrom, choreographed by Albertina Rasch and Bobby Connolly, costumes by Charles LeMaire, directed by Edward Clark, produced by Bobby Connolly and Arthur Swanstrom at the Imperial Theater with Victor Moore, Evelyn Herbert, George Grossmith and Robert Halliday. 56 performances
      - 31 technical drawings (Box 14-9-3, Folder 9)
      - 2 detail drawings (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - 7 photographs of set models (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - 1 program (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Set models
    - George White's Scandals, September 14, 1931:
      Revue in 2 acts, sketches by George White, Lew Brown and Irving Caesar; music by Lew Brown and Ray Henderson, costumes by Charles LeMaire, produced and directed by George White at the Apollo Theater with Edward Everett Marshall, Rudy Vallee, Ray Bolger, Ethel Merman, Alice Faye and Ethel Barrymore Colt. 202 performances.
      - Set notes, 6 p. (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Watercolor drawing of clouds, 16x21 (9x13) cm. (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - 11 technical drawings (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - 68 technical drawings (Box 14-9-3, Folder 10 & 11)
      - Set models
    - The Good Fairy, November 24, 1931:
      Comedy in 3 acts by Ferenc Molnar, English text by Jane Hinton, music by Alexander Haas, staged and produced by Gilbert Miller at the Henry Miller Theater with Helen Hayes, Paul McGrath and Walter Connolly. 151 performances. Revived with a different cast November 17, 1932 for 72 performances.
      - 1 property plot, 4p. (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - 1 rough set sketch (Box 14-9-3, Folder 12)
      - 7 technical drawings (Box 14-9-3, Folder 12)
      - 1 ad (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - 1 program (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Set model
    - Mad Hopes, May, 1932:
      Pre-Broadway tryout of Romney Brent play produced by Curran and Belasco at the Belasco Theater in Los Angeles with Billie Burke, Peg Entwhistle and Humphrey Bogart.
      - (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - 2 ground plans (Box 14-9-3, Folder 13)
    - Music in the Air, November 8, 1932:
      Musical comedy in 2 acts, book and lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Jerome Kern, costumes by John Harkrider, directed by Hammerstein and Kern, produced by Peggy Fears at the Alvin Theater with Al Shean, Walter Slezak and Katherine Carrington. 144 performances, return performance at the Forty Fourth Street Theater, 196 performances.
      - 8 research photographs (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - 13 sketches & notes (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - 2 drawings, watercolor and/or pencil:
      - --Curtain, 25x33 (16x28) cm. (Box B9, Folder 6)
      - --1.4: Weber's Munich office, 25x33 (13x20) cm. (Box B9, Folder 7)
      - --Bedroom with table, 27x40 (14x20) (Box B9, Folder 7A)
      - --II.4: dressing room, 29x39 (12x20) cm. (Box B9, Folder 7B)
      - 46 plans (Box 14-9-3, Folder 14)
    - The Light, 1932-1933.:
      Ottis Lucas had written this pageant to be produced at the Chicago World's Fair in 1933. It was never produced but Urban won a prize for his set model at the 48th Annual Exhibition of the Architectural League of New York.
      - 2 technical drawings, 47x62 cm. (Box D3, Folder 10)
      - 7 drawings, watercolor and pencil:
      - --Rocks, 42x58 (42x58) cm. (Box D3, Folder 10)
      - --4 Rocks, 39x47 (24x32) cm. (Box C3, Folder 4-7)
      - --2 cyclorama, 31x42 (40x42) cm. (Box B9, Folder 8 & 9)
      - Script and letters (Box 15, Folder 12)
        [See also Design: Chicago World's Fair, 1933 and Architectural League, 1933]
    - Musician's Emergency Fund, February 14, 1933:
      Urban designed the setting for a concert of Beethoven's Ninth Symphony conducted by Walter Damrosch in Madison Square Garden for the benefit of unemployed musicians in New York.
      - 4 photographs (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Melody, February 14, 1933:
      Operetta composed by Sigmund Romberg, book by Edward Childs Carpenter, lyrics by Irving Caesar, choreographed by Bobby Connolly, costumes by Charles LeMaire, produced and directed by George White at the Casino Theater with Jeanne Aubert and Everett Marshall, Walter Woolf, Evelyn Herbert and Hal Skelly. 80 performances.
      - Set sketches, 3 p. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Subseries III.4: Ziegfeld Productions, 1915-1932
    This subseries documents Joseph Urban's designs for the producer Florenz Ziegfeld. Ziegfeld never staged a show since their collaboration began in 1915 without some input from Joseph Urban. He designed all the subsequent Ziegfeld Follies and the Ziegfeld Frolics as well as the hit book shows such as Sally (1921), Show Boat (1927) and Whoopee (1928). The subseries contains drawings, research material, technical drawings, photographs of sets and some programs. There are comparatively few watercolor renderings probably because they were given away as gifts by Urban. The productions are arranged in chronological order listed by title, opening date and production information. Production information was pulled from the sources cited in the Theater subseries and from The Ziegfeld Touch cited in the biography.
    - New Amsterdam Roof Garden, 1915, 1917, 1921:
      - Midnight Frolic, August 23, 1915, (1 Photograph of roof garden) (Box B9, Folder 10)
      - Drawing, watercolor and pencil: --Curtain, 24x36 (19x27) cm. (Box B9, Folder 11)
    - Midnight Frolic, 1917:
      - Program, 11/26/17 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Nine O'clock Frolic, February 8, 1921:
      - [No material listed]
    - Midnight Frolic, November 17, 1921:
      - 3 drawings, watercolor and pencil:
      - --Mountain Terrace, 26x32 (19x19) cm., sig. (Box B9, Folder 12)
      - --set piece for horse race, 21x15 (7x7) cm (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - 19 sketches & notes (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - 7 technical drawings (Box 14-9-4, Folder 1)
      - 3 photographs of set drawings (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Ad mockup (Box 14-9-4, Folder 1)
    - Ziegfeld Follies, June 21, 1915:
      Revue in 2 acts, lines and lyrics by Channing Pollock, Rennold Wolf and Gene Buck, music by Louis Hirsch and David Stamper, costumes by Lucile, choreographed by Julian Mitchell, staged by Mitchell and Leon Errol at the New Amsterdam Theater with Ed Wynn, Ann Pennington, Justine Johnstone, Kay Laurell, Olive Thomas, Mae Murray, W. C. Fields, Bert Williams, Bernard Granville, George White, Ina Claire, Lucille Cavanaugh and Leon Errol. 104 performances.
      - Notes and letters, San Francisco Expo, 8 p. (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - 6 photographs, San Francisco Expo. 8 p. (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - 2 photographs, San Francisco Expo (Box 14-9-4, Folder 2)
      - Research on submarines, 6 p. (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - 3 technical drawings (Box B9, Folder 13)
      - 4 drawings, watercolor and pencil, sig.:
      - --House entrance, not used, 24x35 (20x33) cm (Box B9, Folder 14)
      - --Flower curtain, 24x35 (20x33) cm. (Box B9, Folder 15)
      - --Zeppelin, 20x33 cm. (Box B10, Folder 1)
      - --Map for Frisco, 24x34 (20x32) cm. (Box B10, Folder 2)
      - 8 technical drawings (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - 24 photographs of set drawings (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Ziegfeld Follies, June 16, 1916:
      Revue in 2 acts, book and lyrics by George V. Hobart and Gene Buck, music by Louis Hirsch, Jerome Kern and Dave Stamper, costumes by Lucile et al., staged and choreographed by Ned Wayburn at the New Amsterdam Theater with Bernard Granville, Ina Claire, Justine Johnstone, Bert Williams, Allyn King, Marion Davies, Ann Pennington, Lilyan Tashman, W. C. Fields, Fannie Brice and Will Rogers. 112 performances.
      - 2 drawings, watercolor and pencil, sig.:
      - --Globe curtain, 22x31 (18x28) cm. (Box B10, Folder 3)
      - --Opening scene, 24x35 (21x32) cm. (Box B10, Folder 4)
      - 1 ground plan, island (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - 11 technical drawings (Box D3, Folder 11)
      - 15 photographs of set drawings (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Century Girl, November 6, 1916:
      Music by Victor Herbert and Irving Berlin, produced by Charles Dillingham at the Century Theater with Marie Dressler, Hazel Lewis, Hazel Dawn, Irving Fisher, Leon Errol, Elsie Janis, Gus Van, Joe Schenk, Vera Maxwell, Frank Tinney and Lilyan Tashman. 200 performances.
      - 1 drawing, watercolor and pencil:
      - --Bubbles, 24x45 (19x30) cm. (Box B10, Folder 5)
      - --Grand Central Station, 23x28 (20.5x25) cm., sig. (Box B10, Folder 6)
      - 6 technical drawings (Box 14-9-4, Folder 3)
      - 20 photographs of set drawings (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Century Roof Garden, January 18, 1917:
      The producers, Ziegfeld and Dillingham, named the roof garden the Cocoanut Grove and staged a Midnight Revue entitled Dance and Grow Thin, with music and lyrics by Irving Berlin and Blanche Merrill, staging by Leon Errol and Gertrude Hoffman, with Will Richie, Rita Boland, Hattie Burks, Leon Errol, Irving Fisher, Dolly Hackett, and Van and Schenck.
      - Silhouette, unused sketch (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - 17 p. sketches and notes (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - 14 technical drawings (Box 14-9-4, Folder 4)
    - Ziegfeld Follies 1917, June 12, 1917:
      Revue in 2 acts, book and lyrics by Gene Buck and George V. Hobart, music by Raymond Hubbell, Dave Stamper and Victor Herbert, costumes by Lucile et al., staged and choreographed by Ned Wayburn at the New Amsterdam Theater, with Walter Catlett, Lilyan Tashman, W. C. Fields, Bert Williams, the Fairbanks Twins, Eddie Cantor, Fannie Brice, Will Rogers, Allyn King, Delores and Peggy Hopkins. 111 performances.
      - 1 contract letter, 2/7/17 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - 1 set list (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - 2 drawings, watercolor and pencil:
      - --Modern Interior, 20x20 (14x14) cm. (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - --Eagle, 21x26 cm. (Box B10, Folder 7)
      - 12 technical drawings (Box D3, Folder 12)
      - 20 photographs of set drawings (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Miss 1917, November 5, 1917:
      Revue in 2 acts, book and lyrics by Guy Bolton and P. G. Wodehouse, music by Victor Herbert, staged by Ned Wayburn, produced by Charles Dillingham and Florenz Ziegfeld at the Century Theater with Lew Fields, Andrew Tombs, Elizabeth Brice, Marion Davies, Charles King, Bessie McCoy Davis, Vivienne Segal, Vera Maxwell, Van & Schenk, Irene Castle, Bert Savoy, Joe Brennan, Lilyan Tashman, Dolores, George White and Ann Pennington and others. 48 performances.
      - 2 drawings, watercolor and pencil:
      - ---Garden of Eden, 24x29 (22x27) cm. (Box B10, Folder 8)
      - --Swan curtain, 22x22 (19x19) cm. (Box B10, Folder 9)
      - 4 technical drawings (Box 14-9-4, Folder 5)
      - 24 photographs of set drawings (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - 1 program (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Ziegfeld Follies 1918, June 18, 1918:
      Revue in two acts, lines and lyrics by Rennold Wolf and Gene Buck, music by Louis A. Hirsch and Dave Stamper, interpolations by Irving Berlin and Victor Jacobi, costumes by Lucile et al., staged by Ned Wayburn at the New Amsterdam Theater with Eddie Cantor, Frank Carter, Gus Minton, Marilyn Miller, Will Rogers, Allyn King, Dolores, Ann Pennington, Kay Laurell, the Fairbanks Twins, W. C. Fields, and Lillian Lorraine. 151 performances.
      - 3 drawings, watercolor and pencil:
      - --Miniature (spinet scene), 22x33 (13.5x24) cm. (Box B10, Folder 10)
      - --Totem pole, not used, 23x21 (16x18) cm. (Box B10, Folder 11)
      - --Trench, 23x33 (20x31) cm. (Box B10, Folder 12)
      - 8 technical drawings (Box D4, Folder 1)
      - 18 photographs of set drawings (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Program, 7/29/18 and program pages (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - By Pigeon Post, November 25, 1918:
      Play in three acts by Austin Page at the Cohan Theater with Jerome Patrick, Frank Kemble Cooper, John Sainpolis, Phoebe Foster and Peggy O'Neil. 24 performances.
      - 4 p. of program (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Ziegfeld Follies of 1919, June 16, 1919: